[
  { "id": 1, "question": "If it ___ tomorrow, we will stay home.", "choices": ["rain", "rains", "raining", "raines"], "answer": "rains" },
  { "id": 2, "question": "She has lived here ___ 2010.", "choices": ["not yet", "to", "for", "since"], "answer": "since" },
  { "id": 3, "question": "I ___ my homework before dinner.", "choices": ["finisher", "finished", "finish", "have finished"], "answer": "finished" },
  { "id": 4, "question": "What’s the synonym of intelligent?", "choices": ["Smart", "Tall", "lazy", " stupid"], "answer": "Smart" },
  { "id": 5, "question": "We ___ when the phone rang.", "choices": ["eat", "is eating", "were eating", "ate"], "answer": "were eating" },
  { "id": 6, "question": "Which sentence is correct?", "choices": ["He don’t like tea", "He doesn’t like tea", "He don't likes tea", "He doesn't likes tea"], "answer": "He doesn’t like tea" },
  { "id": 7, "question": "Choose the correct passive: They build houses", "choices": ["Houses are built", "Houses is built", "Houses are builted", "Houses is builted"], "answer": "Houses are built" },
  { "id": 8, "question": "Which is a countable noun?", "choices": ["Water", "Apple", "Milk", "wind"], "answer": "Apple" },
  { "id": 9, "question": "She has ___ friends in London.", "choices": ["a small", "a big", "a little", "a few"], "answer": "a few" },
  { "id": 10, "question": "If I ___ you, I would study harder.", "choices": ["was", "were", "want", "be"], "answer": "were" },
  { "id": 11, "question": "What does borrow mean?", "choices": ["To give something to someone forever.", "To steal something and keep it.", "Take something for a short time", "Give something forever"], "answer": "Take something for a short time" },
  { "id": 12, "question": "We have been waiting ___ two hours.", "choices": ["for", "since", "to", "not yet"], "answer": "for" },
  { "id": 13, "question": "What is the opposite of polite?", "choices": ["Friendly", "Happy", "Rude", "Nice"], "answer": "Rude" },
  { "id": 14, "question": "He asked me ___ I liked coffee.", "choices": ["if", "that", "because", "maybe"], "answer": "if" },
  { "id": 15, "question": "Which is correct?", "choices": ["I am look forward to seeing you", "I looking forward to seeing you", "I look forward to see you", "I look forward to seeing you"], "answer": "I look forward to seeing you" },
  { "id": 16, "question": "What is the comparative of good?", "choices": ["goodest", "more good", "Better", "Gooder"], "answer": "Better" },
  { "id": 17, "question": "Which one is an adverb?", "choices": ["Quickly", "Dog", "Happy", "is"], "answer": "Quickly" },
  { "id": 18, "question": "By the time she arrived, we ___ eating.", "choices": ["are finished", "had finished", "has finished", "finished"], "answer": "had finished" },
  { "id": 19, "question": "Which one means the same as purchase?", "choices": ["Break", "Borrow", "Buy", "Sell"], "answer": "Buy" },
  { "id": 20, "question": "The movie was so ___ that I fell asleep.", "choices": ["exciting", "excited", "boring", "bored"], "answer": "boring" }
]
